# Mihajlo Čabraja

# Software Developer

+436767338133 · cabrajamihajlo@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/mcabraja

I am an experienced software developer with over 2 years of experience, capable of building both the frontend and backend solutions, as well as the mobile applications. I am always looking for opportunities to learn and advance my knowledge and expertise.

#### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

- HTML / CSS / SCSS
- Javascript / Typescript
- TailwindCSS / Bootstrap
- React / Angular / Next.js
- C#, ASP.NET / Python
- Unit testing (Jasmine, Karma)
- MySQL / PostgreSQL / NoSQL
- RESTful API

- · Figma, AdobeXD
- NPM, Webpack
- · Git / Gitlab
- CI/CD

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Austrian Airlines (Lufthansa Group)

Strategic Fullstack Developer

August 2024 - Present

- Built both frontend and backend from scratch for multiple projects using various technologies, such as Angular and Flutter for frontend and .NET and Python for backend.
- Worked on a large scale .NET API alongside a team of experienced backend developers.
- Regularly reviewed other colleagues work and actively participated in discussions about new features and projects.
- Helped younger colleagues and interns with their tasks and gave them helpful directions.

#### **CAKE.com** (Clockify)

June 2023 - August 2024

**Angular Frontend Developer** 

- · Worked on maintaining the codebase and adding new features using Angular and Typescript.
- · Wrote custom SCSS and HTML code in order to enhance the application UI and accessibility.
- Utilized GitLab for version control and code repository management.
- Handled installing and maintaining of dependencies and packages using NPM.
- Actively participated in discussions about potential future features and implementations.

YouTestMe Sep 2021 - Dec 2022

Frontend Developer

- Contributed to designing and implementing new features for both the application and the website.
- Regularly used HTML and CSS to improve UI and resolve bugs on the front-end.
- Gained valuable experience in agile development methodologies and demonstrated effective teamwork.

## **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

### Engineer of Electrical and Computer Engineering – Bachelor (appl.)

Oct 2020 - Dec 2023

Department School of Information and Communication Technologies Belgrade, Serbia

Cambridge English: B2 First (FCE)

Oct 2018

Language level obrained: C1 Belgrade, Serbia